Thomas S. Power Papers
Thomas S. Power Papers
1928-1970
Power, Thomas S. (Thomas Sarsfield), 1905-1970.
22 linear ft.
Papers of the American military officer. Powers was Assistant Chief of Operations, U.S. Strategic Air Forces, 1945; Assistant Task Force Commander for Air Operation Crossroads, Bikini Atoll, 1946; Vice-Commander of the Strategic Air Command, 1948-1954; Commander of the Air Research and Development Command, 1954-1957; and Commander-in-Chief of the Strategic Air Command, 1957-1964. Collection includes communications and writings (1945-1970), correspondence (1945-1970), memorabilia (1934-1970), and organizational records (1928-1969), mostly pertaining to the American Security Council. Notable correspondents include William F. Buckley, Lucius D. Clay, Carl T. Curtis, Donald W. Douglas, Ira Eaker, Joe Foss, Arthur Godfrey, Barry Goldwater, Roman L. Hruska, William R. Kintner, Curtis LeMay, Lyman L. Lemnitzer, Robert S. McNamara, Richard M. Nixon, Ronald Reagan, Francis Spellman, Lawrence Spivak, Stuart Symington, Lowell Thomas, Harry S. Truman, Nathan Twining, DeWitt Wallace, and Thomas D. White, among others.
149530
Biographical History
Thomas Sarsfield Power (1905-1970 was an American military officer who served as both Vice-Commander and Commander-in-Chief of the Strategic Air Command. Born on June 18, 1905 in New York City, he graduated from Barnard School for Boys and entered the Air Corps flying school in 1928, receiving his commission as a second lieutenant in 1929. Early assignments took him to famed air corps fields of the day, including Chanute, Langley and Randolph Fields, where he served as an air mail pilot, a flying instructor and an engineering and armament officer.
In World War II Power saw combat as a B-24 pilot in North Africa and Italy, and in 1944 he was named commander of the 304th Bomb Wing on Guam. He led the first large-scale fire bomb raid on Tokyo in March 1945, initiating new tactics that resulted in massive destruction in the Japanese cities. He served as Deputy Chief of Operations under General Carl Spaatz during the atomic attacks on Hiroshima and Nagasaki.
After the war, Power was named as assistant deputy task force commander for air during the "Operation Crossroads" atomic bomb test at Bikini Atoll. He also served for a time in Washington and London. In 1948 he was named Vice Commander in Chief of the Strategic Air Command, serving under General Curtis E. LeMay, his former commander in the raids on Japan. In 1954 he was promoted to the rank of lieutenant general. He was in charge of the Air Research and Development Command from 1954-1957. In 1957 Power succeeded LeMay as Commander in Chief of Strategic Air Command, a post which he filled for seven years. As head of the U.S. nuclear strike force, including over 1,000 nuclear-armed bombers and hundreds of Inter-Continental Ballistic Missiles, he was never far from the "red phone" connections that could bring him orders from the president to go to war.
During his military career, Power was an outspoken proponent of nuclear deterrence, a policy of peace through the achievement of overwhelming nuclear superiority. He favored patriotism, preparedness, and a tough policy toward the Communist enemy. His views on the nuclear strategy were incorporated in a book in 1958, but Secretary of Defense Neil McElroy refused to clear the draft for publication. As a result, Power gained fame in conservative circles as the author of a "banned" book. He was the sole military man to testify against the nuclear test ban treaty before a Senate investigating committee in 1963.
Upon his retirement in 1964, Power was named board chairman of Schick, Inc., with whom he was affiliated for six years. After extensive revision, his book was published in 1965 under the title Design for Survival. It spent a few weeks on the bestseller lists and helped to make Power much in demand on the lecture circuit, where he called for nuclear superiority and victory in Vietnam. He served on a Veterans for Nixon group for the 1968 presidential campaign. Thomas Power married Mae Ayre in 1936. They had no children. Power died on December 6, 1970.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Thomas S. Power Papers consists of communications and writings, memorabilia, organizational records, and photographs. Virtually all of Power's papers stem from his career in the U.S. Air Force and his activities in the years after his retirement in 1964.
Communications and writings form the bulk of the collection. Dating from 1945 to 1970, this material includes articles and essays, books, book reviews, correspondence, interviews, memoranda, press releases, speeches, statements and miscellany. The articles and essays, which were written by Power on topics of defense and nuclear deterrence, include one guest editorial for the New York Times entitled "In Defense of the Pentagon." The material on General Power's book, Design for Survival, comprises drafts, promotional material, reviews from the news media throughout the country, a signature proof and clippings of its serialization in two major newspapers. There is also a comic-book version, complete with color illustrations of the general. Of special interest is the 1958 draft of the book, unpublished at that time due to the objections of the Secretary of Defense. The single book review is of Curtis LeMay's America Is In Danger.
Correspondence (1945-1970) covers 25 years of Power's career. Among those who wrote to Power are mportant figures in government, business, the news media and the military. Carbon copies of Power's replies may be found stapled to the top of the incoming correspondence. Very little of the correspondence relates to specific military aspects of Power's career. There are letters dealing with social arrangements, notes of invitation and congratulations, and letters on current issues, many of which are from prominent individuals. There is also a substantial amount of correspondence from private citizens who wrote to commend Power's patriotism and dedication and to share their fears of the Communist encroachment with him. The correspondence also reflects Power's close association with top levels of defense-oriented corporations, particularly during the years of his service as head of the Air Research and Development Command. A series of letters from Richard Nixon in 1967 and 1968 stem from Power's support of Nixon's 1968 presidential campaign. A Selected Index to Correspondence appears at the end of this finding aid.
The interviews, which date from 1957 to 1970, include a substantial number of transcripts of interviews with Walter Judd of the American Security Council's Washington Report of the Air, as well as a copy of Power's remarks during his appearance on Meet the Press. Of particular interest is the 1966 Viet Nam Review interview in which Power urges escalation and use of air power in Indochina.
The speeches originate from Power's occasional talks as an officer and from his engagements as a speaker after retirement. Power spoke chiefly to Republican clubs, business, civic and patriotic groups. The miscellany section consists of writings of others, most of which are articles on topics of special interest to Power. Specific information regarding Power's lectures can be found on the first page of each draft.
Memorabilia, which dates from 1934 to 1970, contains appointment books, biographical material, commendations and awards, a drawing of the general, a few items of ephemera, newspaper clippings, an obituary and several scrapbooks. The untitled scrapbooks contain a complete and mounted collection of clippings from Power's career.
Organizational records, 1928-1969, contain material from the American Security Council, the U.S. Air Force and the Air Force Academy. Power was a member of the National Strategy Committee of the American Security Council, a private organization dedicated to military preparedness against the Communist menace. The Air Force material consists of records from Power's early career, including commendations, discharge and commission papers, flight books and records, medical records, pilot orders, training papers and material on Operation Crossroads. The Air Force Academy papers date from Power's service on a General Officer Advisory Committee to that institution.
Six boxes of Photographs, 1928-1968, contain both albums and individual photos of a wide variety of subjects. There are a number of photographs from Power's visits to air bases and industrial plants, as well as visits to his command by foreign dignitaries and U.S. Presidents Kennedy and Johnson.
Audio-visual material includes five films, audiorecordings of interview and speeches, and 73 reels of audiotape containing episodes of the American Security Council's Washington Report of the Air, a three-minute daily briefing on current events. Six of these contain interviews with General Power on subjects of national defense.
Other Formats Available
Many of the audiovisual items from this collection have been digitized. Please refer to to access these items.
Arrangement of the Collection
Communications and writings are arranged alphabetically by type of material; within that material is arranged alphabetically by topic or title, with the exception of correspondence, memoranda, and press releases which are organized chronologically. Memorabilia is arranged alphabetically by type. Organization records are arranged alphabetically by name of organization. Photographs are arranged alphabetically by subject. Audiovisual material is arranged by type and within that alphabetically by title.
Subject and Genre Headings
Buckley, William F., Jr., 1925-2008.; Clay, Lucius D. (Lucius DuBignon), 1897-1978.; Curtis, Carl T. (Carl Thomas), 1905-2000.; Douglas, Donald W. (Donald Willis), 1892-1981.; Eaker, Ira, 1896-1987.; Foss, Joe, 1915-2003.; Godfrey, Arthur, 1903-1983.; Goldwater, Barry, 1938-; Hruska, Roman L. (Roman Lee), 1904-1999.; Kintner, William R. (William Roscoe), 1915-1997.; LeMay, Curtis E.; Lemnitzer, Lyman L. (Lyman Louis), 1899-1988.; McNamara, Robert S., 1916-2009.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.; Power, Thomas S. (Thomas Sarsfield), 1905-1970.; Reagan, Ronald.; Spellman, Francis, 1889-1967.; Spivak, Lawrence E. (Lawrence Edmund), 1900-1994.; Symington, Stuart, 1901-1988.; Thomas, Lowell, 1892-1981.; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.; Twining, Nathan F. (Nathan Farragut), 1897-1982.; Wallace, DeWitt, 1889-1981.; White, Thomas D. (Thomas Dresser), 1901-1965.; American Security Council.; United States. -- Air Force.; United States. -- Air Force -- Officers.; United States. -- Air Force. -- Strategic Air Command.; Design for survival.; Aeronautics, Military -- United States.; Arms race.; Deterrence (Strategy); United States -- History, Military -- 20th century.; United States -- Military policy.; 16mm (photographic film size); Appointment books.; Clippings (information artifacts); Sound recordings.; Book reviews.; Correspondence.; Interviews.; Manuscripts for publication.; Memorandums.; Phonograph records.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Scrapbooks.; Speeches (documents); Aeronautics.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of General Thomas S. Power and and Mrs. Thomas S. Power, 1964-1971.
Inventory
- Communications and writings
  - Articles and essays
    - Notes (Box 1)
    - "Commander's Farewell," Combat Crew, Dec 1964 (Box 1)
    - "Deterrence or Defeat?" Ordnance, Nov-Dec 1968 (Box 1)
    - "In Defense of the Pentagon," New York Times, May 23, 1970 (Box 1)
    - "The Nature of the Deterrent System," Air Force, Mar 1965 (Box 1)
    - "A New Strategic Bomber?", typescript reproduction (Box 1)
  - Book, Design for Survival
    - Comic-book version, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Draft, 1958; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Excerpts, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Promotional Material, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Reviews, 1965; 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Signature Proof, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Serialization, Los Angeles Times, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Serialization, Philadelphia Inquirer (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - Book review, America is in Danger, Curtis E. LeMay, National Review, Aug 1968 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence
    - Undated (Box 2)
    - [General], 1945-1952 May; 75 folders (Box 2)
    - [General], 1952 Jun-1957 Jun; 61 folders (Box 3)
    - [General], 1957 Jul-1959; 30 folders (Box 4)
    - [General], 1960-1962; 38 folders (Box 5)
    - [General], 1963-1964 Oct; 24 folders (Box 6)
    - [General], 1964 Nov-1968 Jul; 43 folders (Box 7)
    - [General], 1968 Aug-1970; 18 folders (Box 8)
  - Interviews
    See also Audiovisual material: Phonograph records: Thomas S. Power interviews.
    - American Security Council Washington Report of the Air
      Listed here are transcripts. See Audiovisual material: Tapes for original recordings of these and other episodes featuring Power.
      - On the changing strategic military balance, 1967 (Box 8)
      - with Elias Demetracopoulos, 1964 (Box 8)
      - with Elias Demetracopoulos, 1966 (Box 8)
      - with Kenneth Leish, 1968 (Box 8)
      - Meet the Press, 21 Mar 1965 (Box 8)
    - U.S. News and World Report, 20 Dec 1957; 25 Jan 1965; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Viet Nam Review, Oct 13, 1966 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 8)
  - Memoranda, 1945-1964 (Box 8)
  - Press releases, 1962-1964 (Box 8)
  - Speeches
    See also Audiovisual material: Tapes: Public Affairs Luncheon, Omaha Chamber of Commerce.
    - Contracts, Harry Walker Inc., 1965 (Box 8)
    - Drafts, 1957-1959; 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Drafts, 1960-1968; 8 folders (Box 9)
    - Drafts, undated (Box 9)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 9)
    - Outline for informal remarks (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
  - Statement, House Armed Services Committee Hearing on Reductions of Manned Bombers, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Miscellany
    - "A-2" / "Jap Flak vs the B-29", circa 1945 (Box 10)
    - Kintner, William R. / "A Missile Moratorium?", 1968 (Box 10)
    - Kintner, William R. / "Debacle Road", 1968 (Box 10)
    - Kintner, William R. / "U.S. Overseas Defense Commitments Now and in the 1970's", 1968 (Box 10)
    - Kintner, William R. / "The United States-Soviet Non-Proliferation Treaty" (Box 10)
    - Libby, W. F. / "Man and the Physical World", 1968 (Box 10)
    - Libby, W. F. / "The Moon Base", 1967 (Box 10)
    - Schlafly, Phyllis / "The Twelve Big Gaps in Our Defense", 1968 (Box 10)
    - Strausz-Hupé, Robert / "On the Southeast Asian Confrontation", 1968 (Box 10)
    - Strausz-Hupé, Robert / "Analysis of the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty", 1968 (Box 10)
- Memorabilia
  - Appointment books, 1955-1964; 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Biographical, 1954-1965 (Box 10)
  - Commendations and awards, 1945-1965 (Box 10)
  - Commendations and awards, 1945-1965 (Box 11)
  - Commendations and awards (oversize), 1945-1964 (Oversize 1)
  - Commendations and awards (oversize), 1945-1964 (Oversize 2)
  - Commission certificates, 1929-1951 (Oversize 1)
  - Drawing (Box 11)
  - Ephemera, 1945-1965 (Box 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1945-1965 (Box 11)
  - Obituary, Air Force and Space Digest, Jan 1971 (Box 11)
  - Scrapbooks
    - The Air Battle of Ploesti, 1944 (Oversize 3)
    - My Eight Days in Moscow, 1956 (Oversize 4)
    - USTAF, 1943-1945; highlights the air campaign over Japan from bases in the Marianas (Oversize 3)
    - Untitled, 1934-1959 (Oversize 5)
    - Untitled, 1960-1962 (Oversize 5)
    - Untitled, 1963-1964 (Oversize 6)
  - Sketches, circa 1957 (Oversize 7)
  - Miscellaneous, academic robes, regalia, flags etc. (Box 25)
- Organization records
  - American Security Council
    - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 11)
  - U.S. Air Force
    - Commendations, 1937-1950 (Box 11)
    - Discharge and commission papers, 1929-1948 (Box 11)
    - Entertainment guest lists, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Flight books, 1928-1931; 4 volumes (Box 11)
    - Flight records, 1929-1964; 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Medical records, 1944-1945 (Box 12)
    - Operation Crossroads, 1946-1948 (Box 12)
    - Pilot orders, 1929-1942 (Box 12)
    - Training papers and certificates, 1928-1939 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1929-1945 (Box 12)
  - U.S. Air Force Academy
    - Miscellaneous, 1957-1960 (Box 12)
- Photographs
  - Albums
    - Command Crew (Oversize 1)
    - Dedication Ceremony, Ellsworth Air Force Base (Box 12)
    - 15th Air Force Bids Its Farewell to General and Mrs. Thomas S. Power, 1964 (Box 13)
    - Kodokan Judo Mission, 1953 (Box 13)
    - MacDill Air Force Base, 1954 (Box 13)
    - North Field, Guam, 314th Bombardment Wing, 1945 (Box 14)
    - On Judo, 1951-1953 (Oversize 1)
    - On Judo, 1952; publications by Kudokan Institute, Tokyo; 2 books (Box 15)
    - On Judo, 1951-1952; Offutt Air Force Base (Box 15)
    - Operation Crossroads, 1946-1948 (Oversize 2)
    - Pictorial record of 314th Bombardment Wing accomplishments against the Japanese Empire from 25 February to 15 August 1945 (Oversize 2)
    - President Kennedy's Visit to SAC Headquarters, Offutt Air Force Base, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Reception and Dinner in Honor of General and Mrs. Thomas S. Power, Westover AFB, Massachusetts, 1964 (Oversize 9)
    - [Untitled], circa 1920-1931 (Box 14)
    - [Untitled], circa 1943-1945 (Oversize 4)
    - [Untitled], circa 1945 (Oversize 8)
    - [Untitled], 1957-1962 (Oversize 8)
    - [Untitled], 1962-1964 (Oversize 10)
    - [Untitled], 1962-1964 (Oversize 10)
  - Atomic Bomb Test, Bikini (Box 14)
  - Awards
    - Presidential, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
  - Candids and views, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Judo (Box 16)
  - Kennedy, John F., Elgin AFB, Florida (Box 16)
  - Portraits, 1928-1959 (Box 16)
  - Portraits, oversize, circa 1945 (Oversize 11)
  - Portraits of others (Box 16)
  - Portraits of others, oversize (Oversize 7)
  - Social events (Box 16)
  - Social events (Box 17)
  - Visits
    - Bases and industries
      - Air Research and Development Command, 1957 (Box 17)
      - Anderson Air Force Base, Guam, 1961 (Box 17)
      - Barksdale Air Force Base, 1957 (Oversize 9)
      - Beale Air Force Base, California, 1960 (Box 17)
      - Boeing Airplane Co., 1958 (Box 17)
      - Cambridge Research Center, 1954 (Box 17)
      - Edwards Air Force Base, 1954 (Box 17)
      - Eleuthera, Bahamas, 1956 (Box 17)
      - Fairchild Air Force Base, 1957 (Box 17)
      - General Dynamics (Box 17)
      - International Business Machines (IBM), 1958 (Box 17)
      - Kirtland Air Force Base, 1954 (Box 17)
      - Lincoln Air Force Base, 1964 (Box 17)
      - Northrup Aircraft (Box 17)
      - Oerlikon Machine Tool Works, 1955 (Box 17)
      - Offutt Air Force Base, 1953-1960 (Box 17)
      - Pease Air Force Base, 1957 (Box 17)
      - Raytheon, 1954 (Box 18)
      - Rome Air Development Center, 1954 (Box 18)
      - Schilling Air Force Base, 1957 (Box 18)
      - Thompson Product Museum (Box 18)
      - Western Development Division, Air Research and Development Command, 1957 (Box 18)
      - Wright Patterson Air Force Base, 1955 (Box 18)
      - Vandenberg Air Force Base, 1966 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1957 (Box 18)
    - Individuals
      - Baudoin, King of Belgium (Box 18)
      - Bernhardt, Prince of the Netherlands (Box 18)
      - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1964 (Box 18)
      - Kennedy, John F., 1960 (Box 18)
      - Lodge, Henry Cabot (Box 18)
  - World War II
    - Europe, mainly aerial bombing targets (Box 18)
    - Japan, post-war (Box 18)
    - Pacific Theatre, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Pacific Theatre, oversize (Oversize 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Negatives (Box 19)
- Audiovisual material
  Many of the audiovisual items from this collection have been digitized. Please refer to to access these items.
  - Films
    - Aerial Scenes (83249-2) (KC-Dupe 252), 1947; power_ts_0002; Film: 16mm; color; silent; 1 reel
    - Japan (83249-3) (KC-Dupe 252), 1947; power_ts_0003; Film: 16mm; color; silent; 1 reel
    - Tokyo (83249-1) (KC-Dupe 342), 1947; power_ts_0001; Film: 16mm; color; silent; 1 reel
    - Part I: 1. Guam 2 .Nippon 3. Tokyo (burned out) 4. Cairo, Egypt 5. Greece (1945), power_ts_0004; Film: 16mm; color; silent; 1 reel
    - Part II: 1. Weisbaden, Germany 2 .Paris - Versailles 3. Paris - Pig Allee 4. W.Va. - Power’s and Large’s (1945) (26375403), power_ts_0005; Film: 16mm; color; silent; 1 reel
  - Phonograph records
    - Thomas S. Power interviews, 3/10/1965; 3/21/1965; 1/4 inch audio tape; power_ts_0006; 1 reel (Box 24)
      Side I: General Thomas S. Power (ret) March 10 1965 American Citizens Forum, Civic Auditorium, Omaha, Neb; Side II: General Power, Meet the Press March 21-65 followed by interview on KETV Channel 7 Omaha Neb 3-21-65. Includes some items of ephemera in box with tape.
  - Tapes
    - Public Affairs Luncheon, Omaha Chamber of Commerce, 10/26/1964; power_ts_0081; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel (Box 24)
    - Washington Report of the Air, for Sept. 11 - Sept. 15, 1967; VinylDisc; running time 3:15; power_ts_0007; 1 item (Box 20)
      Side One, Cut 1, For Sept. 11 - Dr. Judd On "Pot And Kettle War: Soviet Reports On China"; Side One, Cut 2, For Sept. 12 - Dr. Judd Interview With Gen. Thomas S. Power On "The History Of Soviet Treaty Keeping"; Side One, Cut 3, For Sept. 13 - Dr. Judd Interview With Dr. Herminio Portell-Vila On "Carmichael In Cuba"; Side Two, Cut 1, For Sept. 14 - Dr. Judd Interview WIth Gen. Thomas S. Power On "Communism And Coexistence"; Side Two, Cut 2, For Sept. 15 - Dr. Judd On "Canada Gets Acquainted With Cuban Communists."
    - Washington Report of the Air, for April 8 - April 12, 1968; power_ts_0008; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For April 8 - Dr. Judd - Crime And Punishment U.N. Double Standard; Tape 2, For April 9 - Dr. Judd - Hanoi’s Organization Of Anti-U.S. Violence; Tape 3, For April 10 - Dr. Judd Interview WIth Gen. Thomas S. Power - Military Uses Of Space; Tape 4, For April 11 - Dr. Judd - Soviet Builds Indian Military Might; Tape 5, For April 12 - Dr. Judd - Eden’s Views On Vietnam.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for April 15 - April 19, 1968; power_ts_0009; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For April 15 - Dr. Judd - The Indian Ocean: New sea of opportunity for Russia; Tape 2, For April 16 - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - New Red penetration in Africa; Tape 3, For April 17 - Dr. Judd interview with General Thomas S. Power - Relying too much on Russian "Rationality"; Tape 4, For April 18 - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. H. Portell-Vila: Upheaval in Panama; Tape 5, For April 19 - Dr. Judd - Free China’s offshore islands: Assets, not liabilities. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for April 22 - April 26, 1968; power_ts_0010; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 20)
      Tape 1, For April 22 - Dr. Judd - Red Liberalization: Czechoslovak style; Tape 2, For April 23 - Dr. Judd interview with General Thomas S. Power - The Atomic Test Ban Peril; Tape 3, For April 24 - Dr. Judd - A British M.P. fears for America; Tape 4, For April 25 - Dr. Judd interview with Edward S. Butler - Nature of the Underground Press; Tape 5, For April 26 - Dr. Judd interview with Edward S. Butler - Composition of the Underground Press. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.